<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Mobify</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Mobify</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">pabloboocastrofeito@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_training_plans">Goals</string>
    <string name="quick_mobility_test_introduction">Welcome to the Quick Mobility Check! This quick assessment will help you identify areas of your body that may need more attention in terms of flexibility and mobility.\nYou’ll be guided through a series of simple exercises that test the mobility of your hips, hamstrings, shoulders, and posture. Each exercise is easy to perform and only takes a few minutes. Based on your results, we’ll recommend the most suitable flexibility and mobility goals for you to focus on.\n\nLet’s get started and discover how you can improve your movement and overall well-being!</string>
    <string name="quick_mobility_test">Quick mobility test</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="finish">Finish</string>
    <string name="app_introduction">Welcome to Mobify, your personalized mobile app designed to enhance your flexibility and mobility. Whether you\'re aiming to overcome stiffness, improve your range of motion, or achieve specific fitness goals, Mobify offers tailored training programs and routines just for you. Start by identifying your areas of improvement, set your goals, and let Mobify guide you through a step-by-step journey to better movement. With easy-to-follow exercises, progress tracking, and daily reminders, Mobify is here to support your path to a more flexible and active lifestyle. Unlock your full potential with Mobify!</string>
    <string name="start_test">Start test</string>
    <string name="quick_mobility_test_onboarding_options_description">Do you want to choose your goals or perform a quick mobility check if you are not clear about them?</string>
    <string name="choose_goals">Choose goals</string>
    <string name="select_goals_title">Select between 1 and 3 goals</string>
    <string name="save">Save</string>
    <string name="next_side">Next side</string>
    <string name="exercise">Exercise</string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>
    <string name="minimum_goals_selection_error">You have to select at least 1 goal</string>
    <string name="maximum_goals_selection_error">You can only select up to 3 goals</string>
    <string name="language_title">Language of the app</string>
    <string name="english">English</string>
    <string name="spanish">Spanish</string>
    <string name="select_exercise_days">Select exercise days</string>
    <string name="monday">Monday</string>
    <string name="tuesday">Tuesday</string>
    <string name="wednesday">Wednesday</string>
    <string name="thursday">Thursday</string>
    <string name="friday">Friday</string>
    <string name="saturday">Saturday</string>
    <string name="sunday">Sunday</string>
    <string name="exercise_reminder_title">Time to exercise!</string>
    <string name="exercise_reminder_text">Remember to do your mobility routine.</string>
    <string name="change_exercise_days">Change exercise days</string>
    <string name="switch_theme">Switch app theme</string>
    <string name="day_not_unlocked_error">Complete the previous day first</string>
    <string name="notification_permission_title">Required notification permissions</string>
    <string name="notification_permission_message">We need your permission to send notifications. Please enable notifications on the next screen.</string>
    <string name="allow">Allow</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="votes_for_your_flexibility">Votes for your flexibility</string>
    <string name="current_streak">Current streak</string>
    <string name="longest_streak">Longest streak</string>
    <string name="your_data">YOUR DATA</string>
    <string name="menu_profile">Profile</string>

    <!-- Quick mobility test -->
    <string name="hip_rotation_test">Hip rotation test</string>
    <string name="hip_rotation_test_description">Sit on the floor with your legs extended in front of you. Slowly rotate your leg inward and then outward while keeping your torso straight.</string>
    <string name="hip_rotation_test_response_easy">Full range of motion with ease</string>
    <string name="hip_rotation_test_response_medium">Some difficulty rotating</string>
    <string name="hip_rotation_test_response_hard">Unable to rotate fully</string>
    <string name="forward_bend_test">Forward Bend Test</string>
    <string name="forward_bend_test_description">Stand with your feet together and slowly bend forward at the hips, trying to touch your toes without bending your knees.</string>
    <string name="forward_bend_test_response_easy">Can easily touch my toes</string>
    <string name="forward_bend_test_response_medium">Can reach just above my toes</string>
    <string name="forward_bend_test_response_hard">Cannot reach my toes</string>
    <string name="behind_the_back_reach_test">Behind-the-Back reach test</string>
    <string name="behind_the_back_reach_test_description">Reach one hand over your shoulder and the other hand behind your back, trying to make your hands touch.</string>
    <string name="behind_the_back_reach_test_response_easy">Hands can easily touch</string>
    <string name="behind_the_back_reach_test_response_medium">Hands are close but not touching</string>
    <string name="behind_the_back_reach_test_response_hard">Hands are far apart</string>
    <string name="wall_extension_test">Wall Extension Test</string>
    <string name="wall_extension_test_description">Stand with your heels, back, and head against a wall. Try to lift your arms overhead without moving your head or back away from the wall.</string>
    <string name="wall_extension_test_response_easy">Can fully extend arms without losing contact</string>
    <string name="wall_extension_test_response_medium">Some difficulty maintaining contact</string>
    <string name="wall_extension_test_response_hard">Cannot fully extend arms without losing contact</string>
    <string name="quick_mobility_test_no_recommendation">Based on your results, we haven\'t been able to determine a clear recommendation since you scored the same on three or more exercises, feel free to choose the objective that best suits your preferences.</string>
    <string name="quick_mobility_test_results">Based on your results, we recommend focusing on</string>
    <string name="and">and</string>

    <!-- Training plans -->
    <string name="hip_mobility">Hip mobility</string>
    <string name="hamstring_flexibility">Hamstring flexibility</string>
    <string name="shoulder_mobility">Shoulder mobility</string>
    <string name="posture_mobility">Posture mobility</string>
    <string name="improve_squat">Improve squat</string>
    <string name="office_worker_daily_mobility">Office worker daily mobility</string>
    <string name="beginner_fullbody_flexibility">Beginner fullbody flexibility</string>
    <string name="beginner_upper_lower_flexibility">Beginner upper-lower flexibility</string>
    <string name="toe_touching">Toe touching</string>
    <string name="thirty_day_pancake_with_pnf_and_loaded_stretching">30 day pancake with PNF and loaded stretching</string>

    <string name="hip_mobility_description">This training plan will help you improve your hip mobility. It is designed to do three workouts per week for four weeks.</string>
    <string name="hamstring_flexibility_description">This training plan will help you improve your hamstring flexibility. It is designed to do three workouts per week for four weeks.</string>
    <string name="shoulder_mobility_description">This training plan will help you improve your shoulder mobility. It is designed to do three workouts per week for four weeks.</string>
    <string name="posture_mobility_description">This training plan will help you improve your posture and spinal mobility. It is designed to do three workouts per week for four weeks.</string>
    <string name="improve_squat_description">This training plan will help you improve your squat. Do a workout before your squat or squat pattern training.</string>
    <string name="office_worker_daily_mobility_description">This mobility plan is designed for individuals who spend long hours sitting and are looking to improve the flexibility and health of their quads, hips, shoulders, and back. In just 8 minutes a day, 3-4 times per week, these targeted exercises help to relieve muscle tension, improve posture, and prevent common aches associated with a sedentary lifestyle. Perfect for incorporating into your daily routine, this plan helps maintain overall mobility and physical well-being.</string>
    <string name="beginner_fullbody_flexibility_description">This full-body flexibility plan is designed for beginners to improve flexibility and mobility throughout the entire body.\nIt is recommended to perform this routine 3 to 4 times per week.\nYou shouldn’t feel pain during the stretches, but discomfort is okay. Always breathe deeply and focus on gradually increasing your range of motion over time.</string>
    <string name="beginner_upper_lower_flexibility_description">This plan is ideal for beginners who want to work on flexibility with a focus on specific areas of the body. The upper-lower split routine allows you to alternate between days targeting the upper body and lower body, which helps to break down the stretches into manageable sessions while focusing on flexibility gains.\nPerform the upper body routine one day and the lower body routine the next, alternating between the two. Aim to do this routine 3 to 4 times a week.\nYou shouldn’t feel pain during the stretches, but discomfort is okay. Always breathe deeply and focus on gradually increasing your range of motion over time.</string>
    <string name="toe_touching_description">The objective of this routine is to be able to touch your toes with straight legs. For the following 28 days do everyday workout 1 or workout 2, you can either choose one and do it every day or change between them. Take a picture of the before and after so you can see the progess made!</string>
    <string name="thirty_day_pancake_with_pnf_and_loaded_stretching_description">Achieving a perfect pancake stretch (where your torso can lay flat between your legs in a seated straddle) requires a combination of passive flexibility, active flexibility, and strength in end ranges. Incorporating PNF (Proprioceptive Neuromuscular Facilitation) and loaded stretching will accelerate your progress by enhancing both your passive and active flexibility while developing strength in deeper ranges of motion.\\n\\n Train 4 times per week for best results, each workout lasts 20-30 minutes.\\n\\nOn week 1 you will build the fundations and introduce PNF Stretching. On week 2 you will introduce deeper loaded stretches. On week 3 you will increase intensity for PNF and loaded stretching and on week 4 you will perform peak training.</string>

    <!-- Exercises -->
    <string name="single_leg_rdl">Single leg RDL</string>
    <string name="deep_split_squat">Deep split squat</string>
    <string name="pancake_stretch">Pancake stretch</string>
    <string name="modified_pigeon_stretch">Modified pigeon stretch</string>
    <string name="standing_hamstring_kick">Standing hamstring kick</string>
    <string name="wide_squat">Wide squat</string>
    <string name="runners_lunge">Runners lunge</string>
    <string name="butterfly_stretch">Butterfly stretch</string>
    <string name="hip_switch_90_90">90/90 Hip Switch</string>
    <string name="standing_pancake">Standing pancake</string>
    <string name="figure_four_stretch">Figure four stretch</string>
    <string name="hip_flexor_stretch">Hip flexor stretch</string>
    <string name="elephant_walks">Elephant walks</string>
    <string name="couch_stretch">Couch stretch</string>
    <string name="seated_hamstring_stretch">Seated hamstring stretch</string>
    <string name="cobra">Cobra</string>
    <string name="duck_walks">Duck walks</string>
    <string name="standing_pancake_good_morning">Standing pancake good morning</string>
    <string name="extensions_90_90">90/90 extensions</string>
    <string name="wall_deep_squat">Wall deep squat</string>
    <string name="cossack_squat">Cossack squat</string>
    <string name="hip_circles">Hip circles</string>
    <string name="modified_horse_stance_stretch">Modified horse stance stretch</string>
    <string name="flat_back_hamstring_stretch">Flat back hamstring stretch</string>
    <string name="hamstring_kicks">Hamstring kicks</string>
    <string name="toe_touch">Toe touch</string>
    <string name="good_morning">Good morning</string>
    <string name="single_leg_hamstring_stretch">Single leg hamstring stretch</string>
    <string name="sit_and_reach_reps">Sit and reach (reps)</string>
    <string name="sit_and_reach_hold">Sit and reach (hold)</string>
    <string name="crossbody_leg_swings">Crossbody leg swings</string>
    <string name="hamstring_chokes">Hamstring chokes</string>
    <string name="roll_down">Roll down</string>
    <string name="crossbody_hamstring_stretch">Crossbody hamstring stretch</string>
    <string name="crossbody_arm_swings">Crossbody arm swings</string>
    <string name="chair_dips">Chair dips</string>
    <string name="dip_hold">Dip hold</string>
    <string name="box_shoulder_stretch">Box shoulder stretch</string>
    <string name="arm_circles">Arm circles</string>
    <string name="chest_pulses">Chest pulses</string>
    <string name="behind_the_back_bicep_stretch">Behind the back bicep stretch</string>
    <string name="door_frame_chest_stretch">Door frame chest stretch</string>
    <string name="shoulder_dislocations">Shoulder dislocations</string>
    <string name="loaded_lat_stretch">Loaded lat stretch</string>
    <string name="bicep_stretch">Bicep stretch</string>
    <string name="cherry_pickers">Cherry pickers</string>
    <string name="side_stretch">Side stretch</string>
    <string name="broomstick_chest_opener">Broomstick chest opener</string>
    <string name="wall_extension">Wall extension</string>
    <string name="pike">Pike</string>
    <string name="wall_lat_stretch">Wall lat stretch</string>
    <string name="wall_angels">Wall angels</string>
    <string name="seated_twist">Seated twists</string>
    <string name="cat_cow">Cat-cow</string>
    <string name="basic_back_lift">Basic back lift</string>
    <string name="lateral_neck_stretch">Lateral neck stretch</string>
    <string name="wall_back_bend_walkdown">Wall back bend walkdown</string>
    <string name="wall_chest_stretch">Wall chest stretch</string>
    <string name="active_twist_hold">Active twist hold</string>
    <string name="lateral_stretch">Lateral stretch</string>
    <string name="cat">Cat</string>
    <string name="cow">Cow</string>
    <string name="lat_stretch">Lat stretch</string>
    <string name="shoulder_external_rotation">Shoulder external rotation</string>
    <string name="thread_the_needle">Thread the needle</string>
    <string name="lunging_lateral_stretch">Lunging lateral stretch</string>
    <string name="shoulder_internal_rotation">Shoulder internal rotation</string>
    <string name="single_leg_rdl_description">Stand with your feet hip-width apart, shift your weight onto one leg and slightly bend the oher. Keep your back straight while hinging at your hips. Use your hamstring to pull yourself back up.</string>
    <string name="deep_split_squat_description">Assume a lunge position with one leg forward and the other backward. Lower your body down and lean forward. Push back up to the starting position.</string>
    <string name="pancake_stretch_description">Sit on the ground and open your legs as wide as possible into a straddle position. Lean forward at your hips, trying to reach as far as you can in front of you. Keep your back straight and chest open.</string>
    <string name="modified_pigeon_stretch_description">Get on the ground with one knee bent in front of you and the other leg behind you slightly bent. Lean into the front knee lowering your upper body toward the ground.</string>
    <string name="standing_hamstring_kick_description">Stand with your feet hip-width apart and extend one arm in front of you. Swing that leg up in front of you and back down while keeping you leg as straight as possible and your toes pointed up.</string>
    <string name="wide_squat_description">Stand with feet wider than shoulder-width apart, toes pointed slightly outward. Lower into a deep squat position, keeping your back straight and chest up. Stand back up to the starting position.</string>
    <string name="runners_lunge_description">Step one leg forward into a lunge position, keeping the back leg extended and the knee off the ground. Sink your hips down and forward to stretch the hip flexors.</string>
    <string name="butterfly_stretch_description">Sit with the soles of your feet together and your knees ot to the sides. Hold your feet and bring them as coles to you as you can. Gently press your knees toward the ground.</string>
    <string name="hip_switch_90_90_description">Sit with one leg bent in front and the other bent behind you. Rotate your hips to switch the position of your legs, keeping both knees at 90-degree angles while switching sides.</string>
    <string name="standing_pancake_description">Stand and open your legs as wide as possible into a straddle position. Then bend at the hips, pushing them back while keeping your back straight.</string>
    <string name="figure_four_stretch_description">Sit on the ground with one leg bent and the other ankle crossed over the opposite knee. Gently pull the leg underneath toward you or press down on the top knee to stretch the hip and glutes.</string>
    <string name="hip_flexor_stretch_description">Kneel on one knee with the other leg bent at 90 degrees in front. Push your hips forward to stretch the front of the hip and thigh.</string>
    <string name="elephant_walks_description">Hinge at your hips until you feel a stretch behind your knees. Bend one leg while the other is straight then fluidly bend the other knee while straightening the first knee.</string>
    <string name="couch_stretch_description">Kneel on the ground facing away from a wall, place one foot against the wall with the knee bent at 90 degrees. Tuck your pelvis and lean slightly forward with your body upright to stretch the hip flexor.</string>
    <string name="seated_hamstring_stretch_description">Sit on the ground with one leg straight out in front of you and the other leg bent in toward you. Reach forward with both hands, trying to touch the toes of your straight leg.</string>
    <string name="cobra_description">Lie face down on the ground, place hands under shoulders in a plank position. Lift your upper body off the ground, arching your back.</string>
    <string name="duck_walks_description">Get into a deep squat position and walk forward, staying low to the ground to stretch the hips and improve mobility.</string>
    <string name="standing_pancake_good_morning_description">Stand with your feet wider than shoulder-width apart and toes pointed slightly outward. Hinge at your hips and lower your upper body towards the ground, keeping your back straight and chest open.</string>
    <string name="extensions_90_90_description">Sit with one leg bent in front and the other bent behind you. Lift your body off the ground while keeping your knees on the ground then lower back down.</string>
    <string name="wall_deep_squat_description">Stand with your back against a wall and lower into a deep squat position. Use the wall for support and gently push your knees away from your body.</string>
    <string name="cossack_squat_description">Stand with feet wider than shoulder-width apart, shift your weight to one side lowering into a squat while keeping the other leg straight. In one motion, return to starting position and switch sides.</string>
    <string name="hip_circles_description">Stand with feet hip-width apart and make circular motions with your hips, going clockwise and then counterclockwise. Gradually increase the size of the circles.</string>
    <string name="modified_horse_stance_stretch_description">Stand with feet wider than shoulder-width apart, toes pointed outward. Lower into a wide squat position, keeping your back straight while pushing your knees out.</string>
    <string name="flat_back_hamstring_stretch_description">Stand with feet together, hinge at the hips, and reach forward along your legs to stretch the hamstrings. Keep your back straight and chest open.</string>
    <string name="hamstring_kicks_description">Stand with your feet hip-width apart and extend one arm in front of you. Swing that leg up in front of you and back down while keeping your leg as straight as possible and your toes pointed up. Repeat with the other leg.</string>
    <string name="toe_touch_description">Stand with your feet close together. Hinge at your hips and lower your upper body towards your toes. Reach your hands towards your feet, try to touch your toes, the ground, or as far down your legs as you can comfortably go.</string>
    <string name="good_morning_description">Stand with your feet more than shoulder-width apart (wider stance) and place your hands on your hips. Hinge at your hips and lower your upper body towards the ground while keeping your back straight then come back up.</string>
    <string name="single_leg_hamstring_stretch_description">Sit on the ground with on leg straight out in front of you and the other leg bent in toward you. Reach forward with both hands, trying to touch the toes of your straight leg.</string>
    <string name="sit_and_reach_reps_description">Sit on the ground with your legs extended straight in front of you. Reach both hands forward, trying to reach past your toes or as far as you can go. Return to te starting position and repeat.</string>
    <string name="sit_and_reach_hold_description">Sit on the ground with your legs extended straight in front of you. Reach both hands forward, trying to reach past your toes or as far as you can go.</string>
    <string name="crossbody_leg_swings_description">Hold onto a wall or something near you for support. Swing one leg across the front of your body, then back and out to the side. Repeat while slowly increasing your range of motion.</string>
    <string name="hamstring_chokes_description">Sit on the ground and bend one leg, bringing your knee toward you. Place your hand behind your hamstring and gently pull your leg toward your chest, feeling a stretch in the back of your thigh. Straighten your leg, extending up toward the celing.</string>
    <string name="roll_down_description">Stand with your feet hip-width apart and slowly roll your upper body forward, one vertebra at a time, until your hands touch the ground as far as you can comfortably go. Roll back up to the starting position in the same controlled manner.</string>
    <string name="crossbody_hamstring_stretch_description">While standing, cross one leg behind the other (keep this leg straight). Reach downward and try to touch the toes of that leg. Slightly bend the other legs so that so can bend down.</string>
    <string name="crossbody_arm_swings_description">Stand with your feet shoulder widthapart and swing your arms across the front of your body until they reach the opposite side, then swing back in one continuous movement.</string>
    <string name="chair_dips_description">Sit on the edge of a sturdy chair and grip the front edge of the seat with your hands. Move your body off the chair and lower to the ground by bending your elbows, then push yourself back up to the starting position.</string>
    <string name="dip_hold_description">Begin like a chair dip by sitting on the edge of a chair with gands in front of you. Move your body off the chair and lower to the ground by bending your elbow. Hold this position, then push yourself back up.</string>
    <string name="box_shoulder_stretch_description">Place your hands shoulder width apart on a chair or counter in front of you. Then, lower your heand and chest towards the ground, feeling the stretch in your shoulders and upper back. Hold for a few seconds before returning to the starting position.</string>
    <string name="arm_circles_description">Stand with your feet shoulder-width apart and extend your arms out to your sides. Make large circular motions with your arms. Reverse the direction of the circles after a few repetitions.</string>
    <string name="chest_pulses_description">Stand with your feet shoulder-width apart and extend your arms out to your sides. Point thumbs back with palms facing up then pulse your hands backward using small, rapid movements.</string>
    <string name="behind_the_back_bicep_stretch_description">Grasp your arms behind your back. Gently pull them up towards your upper back, feeling the stretch in your bicep. Hold for a few seconds before releasing.</string>
    <string name="door_frame_chest_stretch_description">Stand facing an open doorway and place your hands on either side of the doorframe. Lean forward to feel the stretch in your chest and shoulders.</string>
    <string name="shoulder_dislocations_description">Hold a broomstick or resistance band with your hands shoulder-width apart. Slowly raise the stick above your head and behind your back, feeling the stretch in your shoulders and chest. Reverse the movement to come back to the starting position.</string>
    <string name="loaded_lat_stretch_description">Lay with your upper body on a chair or bench. Raise your arms straight up while holding a weight then slowly bring them down to above your head or as far as you can.</string>
    <string name="bicep_stretch_description">Place your hands on a counter or study surface behind you with palms facing down. Lower your body to feel the stretch in your shoulders and biceps.</string>
    <string name="cherry_pickers_description">Stand with your feet shoulder-width apart and extend your arms above your head. Reach one arm higher than the other using your shoulders and upper body, alternate sides.</string>
    <string name="side_stretch_description">Stand with your feet shoulder-width apart and exend one arm above your head. Lean toward the opposite side to feel the stretch. Hold for a few seconds before repeating on the other side.</string>
    <string name="broomstick_chest_opener_description">Hold a broomstick or resistance band with your hands shoulder-width apart. Slowly raise the stick above your head and behind your back, hold the broomstick behind your back, feeling the stretch in your chest.</string>
    <string name="wall_extension_description">Sit on a chair, place hands on the backrest, and gently arch your upper back to push your chest forward. Hold for a few seconds to stretch the front of the body.</string>
    <string name="pike_description">Sit on the ground, extend legs straight in front, and reach forward towards toes, trying to touch them. Keep your back straight and hold targeting your lower back.</string>
    <string name="wall_lat_stretch_description">Stand facing a wall, place your elbows on the wall above shoulder height. Take a step back and lean your upper body into the wall.</string>
    <string name="wall_angels_description">Stand against a wall, bend elbows at 90 degrees, and slowly slide them up and down the wall. Maintain contact with the wall especially elbows and writst throughout.</string>
    <string name="seated_twist_description">Sit on the ground with your legs crossed. Twist your torso to the side, using your arm for leverage, this is a passive stretch. Hold the twist, then switch sides to release tension in the back and spine.</string>
    <string name="cat_cow_description">Get on hands and knees, arch your back up like a cat with your head facing down, and the arch it down like a cow. Flow smoothly from one position to the other.</string>
    <string name="basic_back_lift_description">Lie face down, hands next to shoulders or under your head, and lift upper body off the ground. Lower back down and repeat.</string>
    <string name="lateral_neck_stretch_description">Stand or sit with a straight back, tilt your head to one side, bringing your ear towards your shoulder. You can user your hands to gently pull your head closer to your shoulder.</string>
    <string name="wall_back_bend_walkdown_description">Stand facing away a wall and gently arch your back to place your hands on the wall behind you. Walk them down as far as you are able to.</string>
    <string name="wall_chest_stretch_description">Stand next to a wall and place your forearm against it while keeping your arm straight. Gently lean forward to stretch your chest.</string>
    <string name="active_twist_hold_description">Sit on the ground with your legs crossed. Twist your torso to the side and hold yourself in that position (without using arms for leverage). This is an active stretch.</string>
    <string name="lateral_stretch_description">Stand with feet hip-width apart or sit, and reach one arm overhead. Lean over in the direction of your arm to feel the stretch in your side.</string>
    <string name="cat_description">Get on hands and knees then arch your back up like a cat with your head facing down.</string>
    <string name="cow_description">Get on hands and knees then arch your back down like a cow with your head looking straight.</string>
    <string name="lat_stretch_description">kneel with a chair in front of you and place your elbows on the back of the chair. Lower your head and chest toward the ground.</string>
    <string name="shoulder_external_rotation_description">Sit with straight back then hold a broomstick behind your shoulder. Grab the back of the broomstick with your hand so that your arm is now wrapped around it. Gently pull the broomstick up from the bottom.</string>
    <string name="thread_the_needle_description">Start on hands and knees, reach one arm under your body and across the ground, resting your shoulder and ear on the ground. Hold this position.</string>
    <string name="lunging_lateral_stretch_description">Step into a lunge position, reach one arm overhead, and lean over in the direction of your arm to feel the stretch in your side and hip.</string>
    <string name="shoulder_internal_rotation_description">Stand with your back straight and your hand on your hip. Place your other hand on your elbow and gently pull it forward to rotate your shoulder inward.</string>
    <string name="ankle_band_mobilization">Ankle band mobilization</string>
    <string name="ankle_band_mobilization_description">Place the band in the exact position of the photo (not too high). The band must help you push the talus bone backward.</string>
    <string name="ankle_foam_rolling">Ankle foam rolling</string>
    <string name="ankle_foam_rolling_description">Start by moving slowly up and down the lower leg muscles until you find a tender area. Pause on this area and “tack it down” with your opposite leg for about ten seconds before moving to find another spot</string>
    <string name="ankle_stretch">Ankle stretch</string>
    <string name="ankle_stretch_description">Use a step to place your feet and put one feet back on the edge of the step to stretch the ankle.</string>
    <string name="knee_touchdown_progression">Knee touchdown progression</string>
    <string name="knee_touchdown_progression_description">Increase each time the range of motion to finally be able to do pistol squats to strengthen the knees.</string>
    <string name="hip_band_mobilitazion">Hip band mobilization</string>
    <string name="hip_band_mobilitazion_description">"Start with the band pulled close to your hip joint. Assume a lunge position with the band around your forward leg. The band should be pulling laterally in this position. From this position, rock your knee inward and back ten times. With enough tension on the band, this should cause a light stretching sensation in your lateral hip. Next push your knee out to the side and back."</string>
    <string name="hip_foam_rolling">Hip foam rolling</string>
    <string name="hip_foam_rolling_description">Address your hip flexors, quads and lateral hips. Start by moving slowly up and down the lower leg muscles until you find a tender area. Pause on this area and \"tack it down\" with your bodyweight for about ten seconds before moving again.</string>
    <string name="worlds_greatest_stretch">World\'s greatest stretch</string>
    <string name="worlds_greatest_stretch_description">Start by assuming a deep lunge position with your left foot forward. Squeeze your glutes and drive your hips toward the floor. This movement should cause a stretch to be felt in the front of the right hip. Second, drop your left elbow to the ground. Hold for five seconds. Next, use your elbow or hand to drive your left knee out to the side. Make sure to keep your foot firmly planted on the ground. Finally, rotate the entire upper body up and to the left, ending with the left arm in the air. This last movement helps address the mobility of the thoracic (midspine) that is also prone to stiffness.</string>
    <string name="unilateral_adbuction">Unilateral abduction</string>
    <string name="unilateral_adbuction_description">"To start, place an elastic band around your ankles. Next, assume an athletic single-leg stance. Once in this position, push the hips backward and allow the chest to move forward. This small movement allows us to engage our posterior chain and remain balanced. Once we are in position, kick the nonstance leg out to the side and back in a slow and controlled manner. The distance the leg moves out to the side is not our main concern. Focus on keeping the stance leg in a stable and unwavering position during the entire exercise. "</string>
    <string name="squat_bracing_process">Squat bracing process</string>
    <string name="squat_bracing_process_description">Step 1: Lie on the ground with your back to the floor. Your knees can stay bent for comfort. Step 2: Activate the muscles on all sides of your core, a process called co-contraction. A verbal cue I like to use is to brace yourself as if you were about to receive a punch to the gut. This should create a feeling of firmness around your entire lower torso. Place your hands on your stomach and on your side. You should feel the muscles under your hands tense as they activate. Improper bracing will only activate our rectus abdominus (our sixpack muscle).</string>
    <string name="bird_dog_progression">Bird dog progression</string>
    <string name="bird_dog_progression_description">Step 1: From the all-fours position (quadruped), place a PVC pipe or cane along the back as shown. At all times, the PVC should be in contact with the back to ensure proper spinal alignment. Step 2: Once you find the neutral position, re-create that co-contraction of the core you learned from level one. This bracing effort will create the stability needed for the next few steps. Step 3: Next, lift your arms up toward your head (one at a time) and back toward the starting position by your side. During this arm movement, your lower back should remain in a stable, braced position. It is important to breathe first and then brace your core. Don’t hold your breath during this movement. Let your breath out slowly through pursed lips (as if you have a straw in your mouth). Step 4: Once this stage is mastered, the second step is to perform the movement with one leg at a time. Step 5: The next stage is one where both the legs and arms are moving. Start by moving your right arm and left leg at the same time. Step 6: The last stage is where the arm and leg on the same side are moving</string>
    <string name="zombie_front_squat">Zombie front squat</string>
    <string name="zombie_front_squat_description">Step 1: Assume a front squat position with the bar held on top of the chest and shoulders. Step 2: Take your hands away from the bar and hold them out in front of you. This should look like the starting position of the bodyweight squat. Step 3: Use the proper breathing and bracing pattern to stabilize your core properly. Take a big breath into your stomach followed by a strong brace of your core muscles. Step 4: Next, perform the front squat to full depth while trying to maintain the bar in the same position. In order to stay balanced, the bar must track over the middle of your foot the entire time. Inability to adequately maintain core stability and stay balanced will force the arms to fall forward. This will cause the bar to roll off the shoulders and drop to the ground.</string>
    <string name="prayer_stretch">Prayer stretch</string>
    <string name="prayer_stretch_description">Start in a kneeling position. Sit your hips back on your feet and push your hands out in front of you (one hand on top of the other). Next, let your chest drop down to the floor. Continue to reach with your arms together overhead while you let your breath out slowly. Try to sink your chest toward the ground.</string>
    <string name="corner_stretch">Corner stretch</string>
    <string name="corner_stretch_description">Find a corner in the room you are in. Stand with your arms out to the side in an L position. Place your hands on the walls and slowly push into the corner. Make sure to keep your lower back from hyper-extending during this movement. You should feel a good stretch in your chest the more you push into the corner.</string>
    <string name="upper_posterior_chain_activation">Upper posterior chain activation</string>
    <string name="upper_posterior_chain_activation_description">Start by lying on your stomach with your arms in an L position out to the side. While focusing on your midback, perform a small chin tuck and lift your head off the ground. Hold this position while focusing on activating the muscles in between your shoulder blades for ten seconds.</string>
    <string name="external_rotation_press">External rotation press</string>
    <string name="external_rotation_press_description">Step 1: (Row) Grab a resistance band with your right hand. Pull the band toward you in a rowing motion. Your hand should finish directly in front of your elbow with your arm parallel to the ground. This engages the muscles that stabilize the shoulder blade. Step 2: (External rotation) From this position, rotate the shoulder backward. Your hand should now be facing the ceiling with your elbow bent to ninety degrees like an L. Step 3: (Press) Next, push your hand overhead and hold for five seconds. The muscles that stabilize the shoulder blade should be working hard to keep your arm from falling forward. Step 4: Next, reverse the pattern and return to the start position. Lower the arm to the L position. Rotate forward until your arm is parallel to the ground. Finally, press your arm forward to end the movement.</string>
    <string name="seated_figure_four_stretch">Seated figure four stretch</string>
    <string name="seated_figure_four_stretch_description">While seated in a chair, place your ankle over your opposite knee, keeping your back straight. Lean forward and grab the leg of the chair with your hands to assist in lowering your torso. You can also add weight to your hands to increase the intensity.</string>
    <string name="elevated_hip_flexor_stretch">Elevated hip flexor stretch</string>
    <string name="elevated_hip_flexor_stretch_description">Place your knee and ankle in a straight line on a chair, with the other foot grounded and the leg as low as possible. Perform repetitions by leaning backward and downward, then forward diagonally. Do 10 repetitions and then hold at the forward position 10-30 seconds.</string>
    <string name="prone_scapular_rotation">Prone scapular rotation</string>
    <string name="prone_scapular_rotation_description">While lying face down with your arms extended overhead, lift your arms and move them in an internal rotation towards your back, then return to the starting position through external rotation.</string>
    <string name="kneeling_hip_flexor_stretch_with_knee_flexion">Kneeling Hip Flexor Stretch with Knee Flexion</string>
    <string name="kneeling_hip_flexor_stretch_with_knee_flexion_description">Place your knee on a comfortable surface. Lean forward and bend your knee, holding it with your hand on the same side. Apply pressure as if you were trying to extend the knee, and gradually open up the hip.</string>
    <string name="shoulder_backbend">Shoulder backbend</string>
    <string name="shoulder_backbend_description">Stand with your feet hip-width apart. Extend your arms upward and backward, arching your upper back and shoulders. Hold the position for 10, then 20, and finally 30 seconds, gradually increasing the stretch.</string>
    <string name="spine_backbend">Spine backbend</string>
    <string name="spine_backbend_description">Stand with your feet hip-width apart, gently arch your spine backward, lifting your chest and keeping your hips forward. Hold the position for 10, then 20, and 30 seconds.</string>
    <string name="rear_hand_clasp">Rear hand clasp</string>
    <string name="rear_hand_clasp_description">Stand tall and bring your hands behind your back, clasping your fingers together. Stretch your arms down and backward, opening up your chest and shoulders. Hold for 10, 20, and then 30 seconds.</string>
    <string name="lying_cross">Lying cross</string>
    <string name="lying_cross_description">Lying on your back, extend your arms to the sides in a \"T\" shape. Cross one leg over your body to the opposite side, allowing your hips to twist while keeping your shoulders grounded. Hold for 10, 20, and 30 seconds.</string>
    <string name="wrist_biceps_stretch">Wrist-biceps stretch</string>
    <string name="wrist_biceps_stretch_description">Standing, extend one arm in front of you with the palm facing up. Use your other hand to gently pull the fingers down and back, stretching the wrist and biceps muscles. Hold for 10, 20, and 30 seconds.</string>
    <string name="one_leg_pike">One-leg pike</string>
    <string name="one_leg_pike_description">Standing, place one foot on a chair and stretch your leg as you lean your torso forward, trying to reach the raised leg. Feel the stretch in your hamstrings. Hold for 10, 20, and then 30 seconds.</string>
    <string name="kneeling_lunge">Kneeling lunge</string>
    <string name="kneeling_lunge_description">Kneel with one knee on the ground and the other foot forward. Push your hips forward, feeling the stretch in your hip flexors. Hold for 10, 20, and then 30 seconds.</string>
    <string name="pancake">Pancake</string>
    <string name="pancake_description">Sit with your legs open in a \"V\" shape and slowly lean your torso forward, aiming to touch the ground with your chest. Feel the stretch in your hamstrings and lower back. Hold for 10, 20, and then 30 seconds.</string>
    <string name="butterfly">Butterfly</string>
    <string name="butterfly_description">Sit with the soles of your feet together and your knees falling to the sides. Use your hands to gently push your knees down, feeling the stretch in your inner thighs. Hold for 10, 20, and then 30 seconds.</string>
    <string name="calf_stretch">Calf stretch</string>
    <string name="calf_stretch_description">Place your hands on a chair for support and step one leg back with the heel on the ground. Lean forward over your front leg, feeling the stretch in the calf of the back leg. Hold for 10, 20, and then 30 seconds.</string>
    <string name="bent_knee_to_straight_leg">Bent knee to straight leg</string>
    <string name="bent_knee_to_straight_leg_description">Start with both legs in front of you. Put one heel in a sliding surface and fold the other leg to the side. Pull your trunk onto your thigh and use the quadriceps to slide your foot away. Straighten the back on breath in, press hill down into floor and extend your leg on breath out.</string>
    <string name="standing_split_hamstring_floss">Standing split hamstring floss</string>
    <string name="standing_split_hamstring_floss_description">Bent one knee and raise your other leg. Straighten the leg that is in contact with the floor for two seconds and look down behind you, ideally touching the floor with your hands. Bent and repeat all over until time is over</string>
    <string name="quadruped_hip_circles">Quadruped hip circles</string>
    <string name="quadruped_hip_circles_description">Begin in a quadruped position, on your hands and knees. Keeping your core engaged and your back straight, lift one leg and draw large circles with your knee. Move slowly and focus on controlling the motion from your hip joint. Perform the circles in both directions, and then switch to the other leg.</string>
    <string name="low_lunge">Low Lunge</string>
    <string name="low_lunge_description">Start in a standing position and step one foot forward, lowering your hips towards the ground. Drop your back knee to the floor while keeping your front knee bent at a 90-degree angle. Make sure your front knee is aligned with your ankle. Press your hips forward to stretch the hip flexors. Hold the position and then switch legs.</string>
    <string name="seated_wide_legged_forward_fold">Seated Wide-Legged Forward Fold (Pancake Prep)</string>
    <string name="seated_wide_legged_forward_fold_description">Sit with your legs spread wide and hinge forward from your hips.\nLoaded Stretch Variation: Hold a light weight (e.g., 2-5 kg) or a kettlebell in front of you to add gentle pressure as you lean forward.\nPNF Method: Press your hands or elbows into the ground while resisting with your legs (contract), then relax and sink deeper for 10-15 seconds. Repeat for 2-3 cycles.</string>
    <string name="pigeon_pose">Pigeon Pose (Kapotasana)</string>
    <string name="pigeon_pose_description">From all fours, slide one knee forward and the opposite leg back, lowering your hips. This opens the hip flexors and glutes.\nPNF Method: Press your front knee into the floor for 5 seconds, then relax and go deeper.</string>
    <string name="butterfly_stretch_2">Butterfly Stretch (Baddha Konasana)</string>
    <string name="butterfly_stretch_2_description">Sit with the soles of your feet together and your knees dropping out to the sides.\nPNF Method: Press your knees down with your hands or elbows, resist for 5-10 seconds, then relax and let the knees fall lower. Repeat 2 cycles.</string>
    <string name="standing_wide_legged_forward_bend">Standing Wide-Legged Forward Bend (Prasarita Padottanasana)</string>
    <string name="standing_wide_legged_forward_bend_description">Stand with legs wide apart, hinge from your hips, and fold forward. You can place your hands on the floor or blocks.\nLoaded Variation: Hold light dumbbells or a barbell for gentle weight pulling you deeper into the stretch.</string>
    <string name="active_pancake_lift_offs">Active Pancake Lift-Offs</string>
    <string name="active_pancake_lift_offs_description">Sit in a wide straddle, with your hands behind you or in front of you. Lift one leg at a time off the ground while keeping it straight. This strengthens hip flexors and improves active range of motion.</string>
    <string name="supine_twist">Supine Twist (Jathara Parivartanasana)</string>
    <string name="supine_twist_description">Lying on your back, bring one knee across your body to release the lower back.</string>
    <string name="pancake_stretch_with_weight">Pancake Stretch with Weight</string>
    <string name="pancake_stretch_with_weight_description">Sit with legs as wide as possible. Hold a light weight or kettlebell (3-5 kg) in front of you.\nPNF Method: Push your hands into the floor while resisting with your legs for 5-10 seconds. Relax and lean forward deeper for 15-20 seconds. Repeat 2-3 cycles.\nLoaded Stretch: Allow the weight to gently pull your torso forward while keeping your back straight.</string>
    <string name="deep_frog_stretch">Deep Frog Stretch (Mandukasana)</string>
    <string name="deep_frog_stretch_description">Kneel with knees spread wide, feet out, and hips lowering towards the floor.\nPNF Method: Press knees into the floor for 5-10 seconds, then relax and sink lower. Repeat 2 cycles.</string>
    <string name="elevated_pancake_stretch">Elevated Pancake Stretch</string>
    <string name="elevated_pancake_stretch_description">Sit on a yoga block or pillow to elevate your hips. This helps improve the anterior tilt of your pelvis, allowing a deeper stretch. Hold a weight in front for added load.</string>
    <string name="cossack_squats">Cossack squats (side-to-side squats)</string>
    <string name="cossack_squats_description">Stand with feet wide, then squat down to one side while keeping the other leg straight.</string>
    <string name="butterfly_pose_with_forward_fold">Butterfly pose with forward fold</string>
    <string name="butterfly_pose_with_forward_fold_description">Sit with the soles of your feet together and let your knees drop out to the sides. Hold your feet with your hands and gently hinge forward from your hips, keeping your back straight as you fold over your legs. Hold the stretch for the desired time, focusing on breathing deeply and relaxing your hips.</string>
    <string name="dynamic_lunges">Dynamic lunges</string>
    <string name="dynamic_lunges_description">Step forward with one leg, lowering your hips until both knees are bent at a 90-degree angle. Push back up to the starting position and repeat</string>
    <string name="cossack_squats_with_weight">Cossack squats with weight</string>
    <string name="cossack_squats_with_weight_description">Hold a light dumbbell or kettlebell to add load while moving side to side.</string>
    <string name="active_pancake_holds">Active pancake holds</string>
    <string name="active_pancake_holds_description">Sit in the pancake position and hover just above the floor, engaging the hip flexors and core to hold your torso up.</string>
    <string name="leg_raises">Leg raises</string>
    <string name="leg_raises_description">Do both legs and each leg front and side</string>
</resources>