<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Mobify</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Mobify</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">pabloboocastrofeito@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_training_plans">Goals</string>
    <string name="quick_mobility_test_introduction">Welcome to the Quick Mobility Check! This quick assessment will help you identify areas of your body that may need more attention in terms of flexibility and mobility.\n\nYou’ll be guided through a series of simple exercises that test the mobility of your hips, hamstrings, shoulders, and posture. Each exercise is easy to perform and only takes a few minutes. Based on your results, we’ll recommend the most suitable flexibility and mobility goals for you to focus on.\n\nLet’s get started and discover how you can improve your movement and overall well-being!</string>
    <string name="quick_mobility_test">Quick mobility test</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="finish">Finish</string>
    <string name="app_introduction">Welcome to Mobify, your personalized mobile app designed to enhance your flexibility and mobility. Whether you\'re aiming to overcome stiffness, improve your range of motion, or achieve specific fitness goals, Mobify offers tailored training programs and routines just for you. Start by identifying your areas of improvement, set your goals, and let Mobify guide you through a step-by-step journey to better movement. With easy-to-follow exercises, progress tracking, and daily reminders, Mobify is here to support your path to a more flexible and active lifestyle. Unlock your full potential with Mobify!</string>
    <string name="start_test">Start test</string>
    <string name="quick_mobility_test_onboarding_options_description">Do you want to choose your goals or perform a quick mobility check if you are not clear about them?</string>
    <string name="choose_goals">Choose goals</string>
    <string name="select_goals_title">Select 1 or 2 goals</string>
    <string name="save">Save</string>
    <string name="next_side">Next side</string>
    <string name="exercise">Exercise</string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>
    <string name="minimum_goals_selection_error">You have to select at least 1 goal</string>
    <string name="maximum_goals_selection_error">You can only select up to 3 goals</string>
    <string name="language_title">Language of the app</string>
    <string name="english">English</string>
    <string name="spanish">Spanish</string>
    <string name="select_exercise_days">Select exercise days</string>
    <string name="monday">Monday</string>
    <string name="tuesday">Tuesday</string>
    <string name="wednesday">Wednesday</string>
    <string name="thursday">Thursday</string>
    <string name="friday">Friday</string>
    <string name="saturday">Saturday</string>
    <string name="sunday">Sunday</string>
    <string name="exercise_reminder_title">Time to exercise!</string>
    <string name="exercise_reminder_text">Remember to do your mobility routine.</string>
    <string name="change_exercise_days">Change exercise days</string>

    <!-- Quick mobility test -->
    <string name="hip_rotation_test">Hip rotation test</string>
    <string name="hip_rotation_test_description">Sit on the floor with your legs extended in front of you. Slowly rotate your leg inward and then outward while keeping your torso straight.</string>
    <string name="hip_rotation_test_response_easy">Full range of motion with ease</string>
    <string name="hip_rotation_test_response_medium">Some difficulty rotating</string>
    <string name="hip_rotation_test_response_hard">Unable to rotate fully</string>
    <string name="forward_bend_test">Forward Bend Test</string>
    <string name="forward_bend_test_description">Stand with your feet together and slowly bend forward at the hips, trying to touch your toes without bending your knees.</string>
    <string name="forward_bend_test_response_easy">Can easily touch my toes</string>
    <string name="forward_bend_test_response_medium">Can reach just above my toes</string>
    <string name="forward_bend_test_response_hard">Cannot reach my toes</string>
    <string name="behind_the_back_reach_test">Behind-the-Back reach test</string>
    <string name="behind_the_back_reach_test_description">Reach one hand over your shoulder and the other hand behind your back, trying to make your hands touch.</string>
    <string name="behind_the_back_reach_test_response_easy">Hands can easily touch</string>
    <string name="behind_the_back_reach_test_response_medium">Hands are close but not touching</string>
    <string name="behind_the_back_reach_test_response_hard">Hands are far apart</string>
    <string name="wall_extension_test">Wall Extension Test</string>
    <string name="wall_extension_test_description">Stand with your heels, back, and head against a wall. Try to lift your arms overhead without moving your head or back away from the wall.</string>
    <string name="wall_extension_test_response_easy">Can fully extend arms without losing contact</string>
    <string name="wall_extension_test_response_medium">Some difficulty maintaining contact</string>
    <string name="wall_extension_test_response_hard">Cannot fully extend arms without losing contact</string>
    <string name="quick_mobility_test_no_recommendation">Based on your results, we haven\'t been able to determine a clear recommendation since you scored the same on three or more exercises, feel free to choose the objective that best suits your preferences.</string>
    <string name="quick_mobility_test_results">Based on your results, we recommend focusing on</string>
    <string name="and">and</string>

    <!-- Training plans -->
    <string name="hip_mobility">Hip mobility</string>
    <string name="hamstring_flexibility">Hamstring flexibility</string>
    <string name="shoulder_mobility">Shoulder mobility</string>
    <string name="posture_mobility">Posture mobility</string>
    <string name="improve_squat">Improve squat</string>
    <string name="office_worker_daily_mobility">Office worker daily mobility</string>

    <string name="hip_mobility_description">This training plan will help you improve your hip mobility. It is designed to do three workouts per week for four weeks.</string>
    <string name="hamstring_flexibility_description">This training plan will help you improve your hamstring flexibility. It is designed to do three workouts per week for four weeks.</string>
    <string name="shoulder_mobility_description">This training plan will help you improve your shoulder mobility. It is designed to do three workouts per week for four weeks.</string>
    <string name="posture_mobility_description">This training plan will help you improve your posture and spinal mobility. It is designed to do three workouts per week for four weeks.</string>
    <string name="improve_squat_description">This training plan will help you improve your squat. Do a workout before your squat or squat pattern training.</string>
    <string name="office_worker_daily_mobility_description">This mobility plan is designed for individuals who spend long hours sitting and are looking to improve the flexibility and health of their quads, hips, shoulders, and back. In just 8 minutes a day, 3-4 times per week, these targeted exercises help to relieve muscle tension, improve posture, and prevent common aches associated with a sedentary lifestyle. Perfect for incorporating into your daily routine, this plan helps maintain overall mobility and physical well-being.</string>

    <!-- Exercises -->
    <string name="single_leg_rdl">Single leg RDL</string>
    <string name="deep_split_squat">Deep split squat</string>
    <string name="pancake_stretch">Pancake stretch</string>
    <string name="modified_pigeon_stretch">Modified pigeon stretch</string>
    <string name="standing_hamstring_kick">Standing hamstring kick</string>
    <string name="wide_squat">Wide squat</string>
    <string name="runners_lunge">Runners lunge</string>
    <string name="butterfly_stretch">Butterfly stretch</string>
    <string name="hip_switch_90_90">90/90 Hip Switch</string>
    <string name="standing_pancake">Standing pancake</string>
    <string name="figure_four_stretch">Figure four stretch</string>
    <string name="hip_flexor_stretch">Hip flexor stretch</string>
    <string name="elephant_walks">Elephant walks</string>
    <string name="couch_stretch">Couch stretch</string>
    <string name="seated_hamstring_stretch">Seated hamstring stretch</string>
    <string name="cobra">Cobra</string>
    <string name="duck_walks">Duck walks</string>
    <string name="standing_pancake_good_morning">Standing pancake good morning</string>
    <string name="extensions_90_90">90/90 extensions</string>
    <string name="wall_deep_squat">Wall deep squat</string>
    <string name="cossack_squat">Cossack squat</string>
    <string name="hip_circles">Hip circles</string>
    <string name="modified_horse_stance_stretch">Modified horse stance stretch</string>
    <string name="flat_back_hamstring_stretch">Flat back hamstring stretch</string>
    <string name="hamstring_kicks">Hamstring kicks</string>
    <string name="toe_touch">Toe touch</string>
    <string name="good_morning">Good morning</string>
    <string name="single_leg_hamstring_stretch">Single leg hamstring stretch</string>
    <string name="sit_and_reach_reps">Sit and reach (reps)</string>
    <string name="sit_and_reach_hold">Sit and reach (hold)</string>
    <string name="crossbody_leg_swings">Crossbody leg swings</string>
    <string name="hamstring_chokes">Hamstring chokes</string>
    <string name="roll_down">Roll down</string>
    <string name="crossbody_hamstring_stretch">Crossbody hamstring stretch</string>
    <string name="crossbody_arm_swings">Crossbody arm swings</string>
    <string name="chair_dips">Chair dips</string>
    <string name="dip_hold">Dip hold</string>
    <string name="box_shoulder_stretch">Box shoulder stretch</string>
    <string name="arm_circles">Arm circles</string>
    <string name="chest_pulses">Chest pulses</string>
    <string name="behind_the_back_bicep_stretch">Behind the back bicep stretch</string>
    <string name="door_frame_chest_stretch">Door frame chest stretch</string>
    <string name="shoulder_dislocations">Shoulder dislocations</string>
    <string name="loaded_lat_stretch">Loaded lat stretch</string>
    <string name="bicep_stretch">Bicep stretch</string>
    <string name="cherry_pickers">Cherry pickers</string>
    <string name="side_stretch">Side stretch</string>
    <string name="broomstick_chest_opener">Broomstick chest opener</string>
    <string name="wall_extension">Wall extension</string>
    <string name="pike">Pike</string>
    <string name="wall_lat_stretch">Wall lat stretch</string>
    <string name="wall_angels">Wall angels</string>
    <string name="seated_twist">Seated twists</string>
    <string name="cat_cow">Cat-cow</string>
    <string name="basic_back_lift">Basic back lift</string>
    <string name="lateral_neck_stretch">Lateral neck stretch</string>
    <string name="wall_back_bend_walkdown">Wall back bend walkdown</string>
    <string name="wall_chest_stretch">Wall chest stretch</string>
    <string name="active_twist_hold">Active twist hold</string>
    <string name="lateral_stretch">Lateral stretch</string>
    <string name="cat">Cat</string>
    <string name="cow">Cow</string>
    <string name="lat_stretch">Lat stretch</string>
    <string name="shoulder_external_rotation">Shoulder external rotation</string>
    <string name="thread_the_needle">Thread the needle</string>
    <string name="lunging_lateral_stretch">Lunging lateral stretch</string>
    <string name="shoulder_internal_rotation">Shoulder internal rotation</string>
    <string name="ankle_band_mobilization">Ankle band mobilization</string>
    <string name="ankle_band_mobilization_description">Place the band in the exact position of the photo (not too high). The band must help you push the talus bone backward.</string>
    <string name="ankle_foam_rolling">Ankle foam rolling</string>
    <string name="ankle_foam_rolling_description">Start by moving slowly up and down the lower leg muscles until you find a tender area. Pause on this area and “tack it down” with your opposite leg for about ten seconds before moving to find another spot</string>
    <string name="ankle_stretch">Ankle stretch</string>
    <string name="ankle_stretch_description">Use a step to place your feet and put one feet back on the edge of the step to stretch the ankle.</string>
    <string name="knee_touchdown_progression">Knee touchdown progression</string>
    <string name="knee_touchdown_progression_description">Increase each time the range of motion to finally be able to do pistol squats to strengthen the knees.</string>
    <string name="hip_band_mobilitazion">Hip band mobilization</string>
    <string name="hip_band_mobilitazion_description">"Start with the band pulled close to your hip joint. Assume a lunge position with the band around your forward leg. The band should be pulling laterally in this position. From this position, rock your knee inward and back ten times. With enough tension on the band, this should cause a light stretching sensation in your lateral hip. Next push your knee out to the side and back."</string>
    <string name="hip_foam_rolling">Hip foam rolling</string>
    <string name="hip_foam_rolling_description">Address your hip flexors, quads and lateral hips. Start by moving slowly up and down the lower leg muscles until you find a tender area. Pause on this area and \"tack it down\" with your bodyweight for about ten seconds before moving again.</string>
    <string name="worlds_greatest_stretch">World\'s greatest stretch</string>
    <string name="worlds_greatest_stretch_description">Start by assuming a deep lunge position with your left foot forward. Squeeze your glutes and drive your hips toward the floor. This movement should cause a stretch to be felt in the front of the right hip. Second, drop your left elbow to the ground. Hold for five seconds. Next, use your elbow or hand to drive your left knee out to the side. Make sure to keep your foot firmly planted on the ground. Finally, rotate the entire upper body up and to the left, ending with the left arm in the air. This last movement helps address the mobility of the thoracic (midspine) that is also prone to stiffness.</string>
    <string name="unilateral_adbuction">Unilateral abduction</string>
    <string name="unilateral_adbuction_description">"To start, place an elastic band around your ankles. Next, assume an athletic single-leg stance. Once in this position, push the hips backward and allow the chest to move forward. This small movement allows us to engage our posterior chain and remain balanced. Once we are in position, kick the nonstance leg out to the side and back in a slow and controlled manner. The distance the leg moves out to the side is not our main concern. Focus on keeping the stance leg in a stable and unwavering position during the entire exercise. "</string>
    <string name="squat_bracing_process">Squat bracing process</string>
    <string name="squat_bracing_process_description">Step 1: Lie on the ground with your back to the floor. Your knees can stay bent for comfort. Step 2: Activate the muscles on all sides of your core, a process called co-contraction. A verbal cue I like to use is to brace yourself as if you were about to receive a punch to the gut. This should create a feeling of firmness around your entire lower torso. Place your hands on your stomach and on your side. You should feel the muscles under your hands tense as they activate. Improper bracing will only activate our rectus abdominus (our sixpack muscle).</string>
    <string name="bird_dog_progression">Bird dog progression</string>
    <string name="bird_dog_progression_description">Step 1: From the all-fours position (quadruped), place a PVC pipe or cane along the back as shown. At all times, the PVC should be in contact with the back to ensure proper spinal alignment. Step 2: Once you find the neutral position, re-create that co-contraction of the core you learned from level one. This bracing effort will create the stability needed for the next few steps. Step 3: Next, lift your arms up toward your head (one at a time) and back toward the starting position by your side. During this arm movement, your lower back should remain in a stable, braced position. It is important to breathe first and then brace your core. Don’t hold your breath during this movement. Let your breath out slowly through pursed lips (as if you have a straw in your mouth). Step 4: Once this stage is mastered, the second step is to perform the movement with one leg at a time. Step 5: The next stage is one where both the legs and arms are moving. Start by moving your right arm and left leg at the same time. Step 6: The last stage is where the arm and leg on the same side are moving</string>
    <string name="zombie_front_squat">Zombie front squat</string>
    <string name="zombie_front_squat_description">Step 1: Assume a front squat position with the bar held on top of the chest and shoulders. Step 2: Take your hands away from the bar and hold them out in front of you. This should look like the starting position of the bodyweight squat. Step 3: Use the proper breathing and bracing pattern to stabilize your core properly. Take a big breath into your stomach followed by a strong brace of your core muscles. Step 4: Next, perform the front squat to full depth while trying to maintain the bar in the same position. In order to stay balanced, the bar must track over the middle of your foot the entire time. Inability to adequately maintain core stability and stay balanced will force the arms to fall forward. This will cause the bar to roll off the shoulders and drop to the ground.</string>
    <string name="prayer_stretch">Prayer stretch</string>
    <string name="prayer_stretch_description">Start in a kneeling position. Sit your hips back on your feet and push your hands out in front of you (one hand on top of the other). Next, let your chest drop down to the floor. Continue to reach with your arms together overhead while you let your breath out slowly. Try to sink your chest toward the ground.</string>
    <string name="corner_stretch">Corner stretch</string>
    <string name="corner_stretch_description">Find a corner in the room you are in. Stand with your arms out to the side in an L position. Place your hands on the walls and slowly push into the corner. Make sure to keep your lower back from hyper-extending during this movement. You should feel a good stretch in your chest the more you push into the corner.</string>
    <string name="upper_posterior_chain_activation">Upper posterior chain activation</string>
    <string name="upper_posterior_chain_activation_description">Start by lying on your stomach with your arms in an L position out to the side. While focusing on your midback, perform a small chin tuck and lift your head off the ground. Hold this position while focusing on activating the muscles in between your shoulder blades for ten seconds.</string>
    <string name="external_rotation_press">External rotation press</string>
    <string name="external_rotation_press_description">Step 1: (Row) Grab a resistance band with your right hand. Pull the band toward you in a rowing motion. Your hand should finish directly in front of your elbow with your arm parallel to the ground. This engages the muscles that stabilize the shoulder blade. Step 2: (External rotation) From this position, rotate the shoulder backward. Your hand should now be facing the ceiling with your elbow bent to ninety degrees like an L. Step 3: (Press) Next, push your hand overhead and hold for five seconds. The muscles that stabilize the shoulder blade should be working hard to keep your arm from falling forward. Step 4: Next, reverse the pattern and return to the start position. Lower the arm to the L position. Rotate forward until your arm is parallel to the ground. Finally, press your arm forward to end the movement.</string>
    <string name="seated_figure_four_stretch">Seated figure four stretch</string>
    <string name="seated_figure_four_stretch_description">While seated in a chair, place your ankle over your opposite knee, keeping your back straight. Lean forward and grab the leg of the chair with your hands to assist in lowering your torso. You can also add weight to your hands to increase the intensity.</string>
    <string name="elevated_hip_flexor_stretch">Elevated hip flexor stretch</string>
    <string name="elevated_hip_flexor_stretch_description">Place your knee and ankle in a straight line on a chair, with the other foot grounded and the leg as low as possible. Perform repetitions by leaning backward and downward, then forward diagonally. Do 10 repetitions and then hold at the forward position 10-30 seconds.</string>
    <string name="prone_scapular_rotation">Prone scapular rotation</string>
    <string name="prone_scapular_rotation_description">While lying face down with your arms extended overhead, lift your arms and move them in an internal rotation towards your back, then return to the starting position through external rotation.</string>
    <string name="kneeling_hip_flexor_stretch_with_knee_flexion">Kneeling Hip Flexor Stretch with Knee Flexion</string>
    <string name="kneeling_hip_flexor_stretch_with_knee_flexion_description">Place your knee on a comfortable surface. Lean forward and bend your knee, holding it with your hand on the same side. Apply pressure as if you were trying to extend the knee, and gradually open up the hip.</string>
</resources>